Psst. Wendy.Kevin.Come here.
嘘(Psst). Wendy. Kevin. 过来这里.
What is it?
怎么了?
Who is that woman? I know her.
那个女的是谁? 我认得她
Which one?
哪一个?
The one in the polka-dot dress.
穿着圆点花纹(polka-dot)裙子那个?
The one with the hair?
头发特别的那个?
The one in the red hat?
戴着红色帽子的那个?
Yes. She looks so familiar.
是的. 她看起来那么得熟悉.
She does.
她是的.
She looks like Meredith Cain.
她看起来像是Meredith Cain.
Of course! That's her. Don't look.
当然了! 就是她. 不要看.
Who's Meredith Cain?
谁是Meredith Cain?
She's an actress.
她是个女演员.
She was in that movie 'Danger Street'.
她在那个电影中 "危险街道"(Danger Street)
She's very famous.
她很有名的.
I don't know her.
我不认识她.
You come from Australia.
你来自澳大利亚.
I can't believe she's here.
我不相信她在这里.
She looks plain.
她看起来相貌平平(plain)
You're joking.
你在开玩笑.
Here she comes. Shh.
她走过来了. 嘘(Shh).
That's not Meredith Cain.
那不是Meredith Cain.
Hi.Can I help you?
嗨. 我可以帮你吗?
Sharon? Sharon Solaye!
Yes?
It's me. Betsy Milller.
是我. Betsy Miller.
Andrew Jackson Junior High?
Andrew Jackson Junior High(初中)?
We were cheerleaders.
我们(那时候)是拉拉队队员(cheerleaders).
"Push'em back,push'em back,wa-ay back!"
I still don't know her.
我还是不认识她